MUHAMMAD RIZKY ANUGRAHA Data Analyst

Tangerang Selatan, Indonesia | Phone: 089644427730 | Email: anugrahamrizky@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/muhammad-rizky-anugraha

SUMMARY

Junior data analyst with 2 years of working experience and a strong skillset in Excel, SQL, and Power BI currently pursuing additional education in data analytics through RevoU and Refocus. Experienced in working both independently and in teams of 2-5 people. Strong communication skills honed through customer engagement. Detail-oriented, organized, quick learner, eager to apply new knowledge and techniques to challenging data problems. Adaptable and able to work independently or collaboratively to achieve project goals.

SKILLS

Excel

SQL

PowerBI

Teamwork

Problem-Solving

Detail-oriented

Adaptable

 Communication Skills

Creativity

Languages: Fluent in Indonesia and English

PROJECT

Refocus (October 2022)

Project: NHTSA Accident Insight 2021

This project assignment from Refocus Data Analyst Course analyzes the NHTSA (National Highway Traffic Safety Administration) dataset about accidents in the United State of America in 2021.

- Cleaned dataset during 2021 from NHTSA (National Highway Traffic Safety Administration)
- Analyzed the dataset about accidents in USA highways with PostgreSQL
- Collaborated in a team to determine critical insight from a dataset and combine all queries into the dashboard
- Created visualization based on the insight of the dataset with Microsoft Excel
- Gave recommendations from insight and presented the insight to the client with Google Slide

RevoU (July 2022)

Project: San Francisco Bike Share Insight

This is a project assignment from RevoU Data Analytics Mini-Course analyzing a public dataset from google big guery on bike share in San Francisco.

- Cleaned dataset from Google Big Query Public Dataset
- Analyzed the dataset and gained insight into Bike Share in San Francisco
- Created visualization based on the insight of the dataset with Google Data Studio / Looker Studio
- Gave recommendations from insight

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Barista | BrewHaus

(March 2022 - February 2023)

- Working individually in bar handling customers, cashier, and beverage
- Managing Cashier cash and inventory with Excel
- · Developing a menu based on supply stock flow
- Maintaining beverages to the correct specification

Barista | Kopine Simbah

(December 2020 - December 2021)

- Working in a team of 2-5 people of the bar and kitchen handling customers and beverage
- Managing Inventory with Excel
- Developing a menu based on supply stock flow
- Maintaining beverages to the correct specification

EDUCATION

Universitas Sumatera Utara (August 2013 - January 2020) Bachelor of Engineering, Architecture - Cumulative GPA 3.11 / 4.0

CERTIFICATION

Data Analytics Course - Core Track

(November 2022)

Refocus

Data Analytics Mini Course Course

(July /2022)

RevoU